National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; 1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; 1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Hill, Donetta (PA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Hill, Mack (TX), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Hill, Michael (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Hill, Paul (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Hinton, Eric Lamot (CA), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Hitchcock, James E. (FL), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Hittle, Daniel (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Hochstein, Peter (NE), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Hodge, Benny Lee (KY), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Hodges, Henry Eugene (TN(, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 152)
    - Hoffner, Timothy (OH), Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 153)
    - Hogue, Jerry Lee (TX), 1998 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 154)
    - Hoke Sr., Ronald (VA), 1996; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Holladay, Glenn (AL), 2001; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Holland, Gerald James (MS), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Holland, William (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Holloway, Arnold (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Holloway, Allen (OH), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Holloway, Duane (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Holmes, James Williams (AR) Executed August 3, 1994, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Holmes, Karl (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Holton, Daryl (TN), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Hood, Charles (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Hooper, Courtney (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Hooper, George (TX), 1991; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Houston, Eric (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Hovarter, Jackie Ray (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Hovey, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Howard, Alphonso (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Howard, Gary Lee (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Howard, Melvin K. (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Howard, Ronald (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Howard, Stacey Dean (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Hoyos, Jamie Armando (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Hudson, Timothy C. (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Huggins, Michael (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Hughes, Billy George (TX), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Hughes, Preston (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Hughes, Robert 4th (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Hunt, Diedre (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Hunt, Gregory (AL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Hunt, Henry (NC), 2003; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Hunt, Flint (MD), 1996; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Hurles, Richard (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Hude, David O'Neal (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Ibarra, Ramiro Rubi (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Ingram, Nicky (GA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Isa, Marie (MO), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Isaazs, Carl (GA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Jablonski, Phillip (CA), 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Jackson, Andrea (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Jackson, Earl (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Jackson, Etheria V. (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Jackson, Henry Curtis Jr. (MS), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Jackson, Michael Anthony (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Jackson, Noel (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Jackson, Robert W. (DE), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Jackson, Tommy (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - James, Antonio (LA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - James, Terrance (OK), 2001 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Jasper, Alfred (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Jeffers, Jim (AZ), 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Jenkins, Daniel Steven (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Jenkins, Mark (AL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Jennings, Bryan (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Jennings, Michael Wayne (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Jennings, Wilbur (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Jermyn, Frederic (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Johns, Stephen K. (MO), 2001 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Johnsen, Brian David (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Johnson, Carl (TX) Executed September 19, 1995, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Johnson, David (AR), 2000; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Johnson, Don (TN), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Johnson, Dorsie Lee (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Johnson, Edward E. (MS), 2005 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Johnson, Edward James [Eddie J.] (TX) Executed June 17 1997, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Johnson, Emanuel (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Johnson, Erskine (TN), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Johnson, Gregory S. (IN), 1992; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Johnson, James (MO), 2001 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Johnson, Joe (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Johnson, Laverne (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - Johnson, Malcolm Rent (OK), 1993; 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - Johnson, Mark David (OK), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - Johnson, Marvin (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - Johnson, Richard (SC), 1999; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Johnson, Roderick A. (PA), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Johnson, Ronnie (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Johnson, Vincent (OK), 2001 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Johnson, Willie Darnell (CA), 1993; 1996; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Johnson, David (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Johnson, Timothy (MO), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Jones, Aaron "AJ" (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Jones, Brandon Astor (GA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Jones, Clarence (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Jones, Claude (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Jones, Damon (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Jones, Donald A. (SC), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Jones, Earl Preston (CA), 1991 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Jones, Gilbert (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - Jones, James (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Jones, Leo A. (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Jones, Raymond (TX), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Jones, Ronald (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Jones, William R. (MO), 1993; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Joseph, Jason (VA), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Joubert, John (NE), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Karis, James Leslie, Jr. (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Keenan, Maurice J. (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Keene, Marvellous (OH), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Keith, David (MT), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Kennedy, Jerry (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Kennedy, Victor (AL), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Kiles, Alvie C. (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Kilgore, Bruce (MO), 1999 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Kimble, Eric B. (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Kinder, Brian (MO), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Kindler, Joseph (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - King, Amos (FL), 2001; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - King, Carolyn Ann (PA), 1998 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - King, Danny L. (VA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - King, Tommy Lee (TN), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Kirk Patrick Jr., William (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Kitchens, William (TX), 2000 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Knapp, John (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Knight, Charles (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Knighton, Robert W. (OK), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Kokal, Gregory (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Kokoraleis, Andrew (IL), 1999; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Kraft, Randy (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Kreutzer, Paul (MO), 2002 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Kvenzel, William (AL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Lackey, Clarence (TX), 1996; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Lafevers, Lloyd (OK), 2000 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Laird, Richard (PA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Lamb, Michael (TX), 1999; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Lambert, Michael (IN), 2005 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Land, Michael Jeffrey (AL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Landrigan, Jeffrey (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Lang, Kenneth (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Langford, Terry A. (MT), 1998; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - LaGrand, Karl and walter (AZ) [1 of 2], 1998; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - LaGrand, Karl and walter (AZ) [2 of 2], 1998; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - LaRette, Anthony Joe (MO), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Lark, Robert (PA), 1994; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Larzelere, Virginia (FL), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Lauti, Aua (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Lawrence, John (TX), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Lawrie, David (DE), 1999; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Lawson, David (NC) Executed June 16, 1994, Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Lawton, Stacey (TX), 2000 (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Lee, Chad Alan (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Lee, Darrell (AZ), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Lee, Donna (CA), Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Leisure, David (MO), 1999; Undated (Box 5 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Leisure, David (MO), 1999; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Leonard, Eric Royce (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Lesko, John Charles (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Lester, Emmanuel (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Letner, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Albert (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Lewis, John Irving (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Lewis, Reginald (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Lightbourn, Ian (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Lightsey, Christopher Charles (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Lingar, Stanley (MO), 2001; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Lipham, William Anthony (GA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Little, William (TX), 2004 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Livaditis, Steven (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Livingston, Charlie (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Logan, Ronald (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Lonchar, Larry (GA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Long, David (TX), 1999 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Long, Michael Edward (OK), 1998 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Lopez, Eduardo (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Lorraine, Charles (OH), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Lovell, Ivan (MD), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Loving, Dwight J. (Military), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Lovitt, Robin (VA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Lowenfield, Leslie (LA), 2005 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Lowery, Jim (IN), 2001 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Lucas, Cecil (SC), 1996; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Lucas, David Allen (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Lucas, Henry (TX), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Lucero, Phillip (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Lucky, Darnell (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Lundgren, Jeffrey (OH), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Lynch, Franklin (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Mack, Jimmy (MS), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Mackall, Tony (VA), 1998; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Madden, Robert (TX), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Magwood, Billy Joe (AL), 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Maharaj, Krishna (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Majors, James (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Malicoat, James (OK), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Malone, Kelvin (MO), 1998 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Malone, Kelvin Shelby (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Malvo, John (VA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Mann, Fletcher Thomas (TX) Executed June 1, 1995, Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Mann, Larry (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Manning, Warren (SC), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 46)
    - Manriquez, Abelino (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 47)
    - Marek, John (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 48)
    - Marks, Delaney (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 49)
    - Marlow, James G. (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 50)
    - Marshall, Jerry (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 51)
    - Marshall, Jerome (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 52)
    - Martin, James Lewis (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 53)
    - Martin, Leslie (LA), 2002 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 54)
    - Martin, Nollie Lee (FL), 2005 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 55)
    - Martinez, Alexander Rey (TX), 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 56)
    - Martinez-Villareal, Ramon (AZ), 1997; 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 57)
    - Massie, Robert Lee (CA), 2001; 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 58)
    - Mason, Thomas (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 59)
    - Mata, Luis (AZ), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 60)
    - Matheney, Alan L. (IN), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 61)
    - Mathenia, Charles L. (MO), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 62)
    - Matthews, Earl (SC), 1997; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 63)
    - Matthews, Kevin, aka Al Peoples (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 64)
    - Maturana, Claude Eric (AZ), 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 65)
    - Maxwell, William (AR), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 66)
    - Maye, Cory (MS), 2006; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 67)
    - Mayfield, Demetrie (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 68)
    - Maynard, Anson (NC), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 69)
    - Maurer, Donald (OH), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 70)
    - McBride, Michael (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 71)
    - McCall, Edward (AZ), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 72)
    - McCarthy, Curtis (OK), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 73)
    - McClain, Herbert Jr. (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - McConnell, Robert (NV), 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - McCullum, Thomas (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - McDermott, Maureen (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - McFadden, Jerry (TX), 1999 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - McFarland, Frank (TX), 1998 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - McGahee, Earl Jerome (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - McGinn, Ricky (TX), 2000 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - McGinnis, Glen Charles (TX), 1999 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - McGowan, James (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - McKinney, James (AZ), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - McNair, Willie (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - McNeil, Christopher (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - McPeters, Ronald Avery (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - McQueen, Harold (KY), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - McVeigh, Timothy (FED), 2001; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - McWilliams, James (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Medina, Efren (AZ), 1996; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Medina, Pedro (FL), 2005 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - Medina, Teofilo (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - Medlock, Floyd (OK), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - Medlock, Floyd (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - Meeks, Douglas (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Melson, Robert Bryant (AL), 1996 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Melton, James Andrew (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Memro, Reno (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Mendoza, Manuel (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Mendyk, Todd (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Merck, Troy (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Messiah, Keith (LA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Mickey, Douglas (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Mickle, Danny (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Middlebrooks, Donald Ray (TN), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Middleton, Frank (SC), 1996; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Mike, Debra (AZ), 1998; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Mikeel, William (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Miles, Kenyatta (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Miles, Kevin Artice (AZ), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Miller, Donald (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Miller, Don Ray (AZ), 2000; 2005; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Miller, Gary (TX), 2000 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Mills, Gregory (FL), 2001; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Mills, Jon Jeffrey (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Mills, Jr., John (FL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Mincey, Terry Michael (GA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Minnick, William (IN), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Moeller, Donald (SD), 1992 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Moffett, Jesse (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Monroe, Ronald (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Monterroso, Christian (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Montgomery, Williams T. (OH), 2000; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Montiel, Richard Galvan (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Montoya, Irineo (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Montoya, Ramon (TX) Executed March 25, 1993, Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Moody, John (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Moody, Robert Joe (AZ), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Moody, Walter LeRoy (AL), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Moon, Richard (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Moore, Brian Keith (KY), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Moore, Blanche (NC), 1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Moore, Carey Dean (NE), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Moore, Charles Edward, Jr. (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Moore, Curtis (TX), 2002 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Moore, Frank (AR), 1996 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Moore, Lee Edward, Jr. (OH), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Moore, Mark (MO), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Moore, Michael (TX), 2001 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Moore, Richard (IN), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Moore, Scotty (OK), 1999; Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Moore, Tyvone V. (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
    - Moore, William (GA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 144)
    - Moran, Richard Allan (NV) Executed April 10, 1996, Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 145)
    - Moran, Willard (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 146)
    - Moreland, James (TX), 1999 (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 147)
    - Morelos, Vladamir Fred (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 148)
    - Morgan, Edward Patrick (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 149)
    - Morris, Kelvin (PA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 150)
    - Morrison, Jesse (CA), Undated (Box 6 (1-Case Files), Folder 151)
    - Mueller, Everett (VA), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Muhammed, Yuhanni (FL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Mumia, Abu-Jamal (PA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Mu'Min, Dawud (VA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Muniz, Pedro (TX), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Mario (VA), 1997; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Murray, Robert (AZ), 1999 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Narvaiz, Leopoldo Jr. (TX) Executed June 26, 1998, Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Nash, Viva Leroy (AZ), 1996 (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Nave, Emmett (MO), 1996; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Neelley, Judith (AL), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Nelson, David (AL), 1996; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Leslie (NJ), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Newborn, Lorenzo (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Newton, Frances (TX), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Nguyen,Tuan Anh (OK), 1994; 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Nichols, Harold Wayne (TN), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Nicolaus, Robert (CA), Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Nobles, Johnathan (TX), 1998; Undated (Box 7 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)